Rain hammered the city
like it owed money.
You're late, detective.
Traffic. And a body
on the Fifth Street bridge.
The same bridge as last month?
Same bridge, same caliber,
same note in the pocket.
So we have a pattern.
We have a problem.
The mayor's office called twice.
Let them call a third time.
I don't chase headlines.
I chase the truth.
The truth doesn't pay
your pension, Reyes.
Neither does looking
the other way.
What did the note say this time?
One word, same as before:
"Remember."
Remember what?
That's the question.
No. The question is
who wants us to forget.
Get some sleep.
Tomorrow we visit the archive.
The archive burned down
in '09, captain.
Officially, it did.
Officially.